https://www.techtree.com/content/legal-stuff.html

Home
Privacy PolicyInformation Collection And Use - The only personal information that Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd collects about you when you use our website is what you tell us about yourself or information you provide to us through the Feedback section or when you send us an e-mail.As most websites do, however, we do track usage patterns on an anonymous basis. Your identity cannot reasonably be ascertained from this information. Each time you visit our site, our server records your Internet Service Provider, the date and time of your visit, the pages you visit and the documents downloaded, the searches you performed, and the referring URLs you came from. We use this non-personal information to optimize our service.For your convenience, we may offer links from our site to other websites. However, Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd is not responsible for, nor do we accept any liability for, the personal information collection, use and disclosure practices of other entities to which our site may link. You should consult the privacy policies of these other entities before providing any personal information on their sites.Your Consent - We collect, use and disclose your personal information with your consent or as permitted or required by law. Your consent may be express or implied, depending on the circumstances and the sensitivity of the personal information in question. If you provide personal information about another person to us, we assume you have the consent of that individual to enable us to collect, use or disclose their information as described in this policy. If you choose to provide personal information to Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd, we assume that you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this privacy statement.If you do not consent, please do not provide your personal information or, where applicable, exercise the opt-in or opt-out options offered. Subject to legal and contractual requirements and reasonable notice, you may refuse to consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information or you may withdraw your consent to our further collection, use and disclosure of information about you, by contacting us.Security - Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd has implemented reasonable physical, organizational and technological security measures to safeguard the personal information in our custody or control. These include safeguards to protect personal information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification.Changes To This Statement - Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time and we will take reasonable steps to advise affected individuals of any material changes, if necessary. However, you should review this privacy statement from time to time to ensure that you are aware of and accept any changes made. You may contact us here to obtain a current copy of this privacy statement.Registration - No registration is required to view the TechTree.com website. However, if you choose to register or provide personal information on our newsletter sign-up, feedback forms, affiliate, partner and job application pages or other areas of our site, we will ask for information which may include your name, email address, company name, and phone number.Email Alerts - If a user wishes to subscribe to our alerts, updates, briefings etc, we ask for contact and delivery information such as name and e-mail address. All of these e-mail lists provide opt-out facilities online and with each e-mail broadcast. In some cases, the user is asked to provide optional demographic and personal interest information that is used to keep our content as relevant as possible.Sharing - We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.Cookies - A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of cookies is for the convenience of visitors. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user does not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users in order to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to, or control over, these cookies.  Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet and use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.Log Files - We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track a user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.Links - Some of our websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.Surveys And Contests - From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as sex and age). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.Recommend This Site - If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site or page, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the webpage. This information is not stored except for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail.Special Offers - New members will receive a welcome e-mail to verify the password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Where this is the case, we present the option to not receive these types of communications at the point of sign-up.Site And Service Updates - We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone.Correction \ Updating Personal Information - If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can be done at the registration page or by e-mailing the site editor. Many of our sites will offer subscribers an account management facility that will allow them to change or amend their own records.Choice \ Opt-Out - Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. Users who no longer wish to receive a newsletter \ alert \ briefing may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.Notification Of Changes - If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will seek to advise all users of these changes.Legal Disclaimer - Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our website.Terms of Content UseTHE CONTENT HEREIN AND THE RESEARCH MATERIAL ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTY AND REPRESENTATION OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AND NEITHER TRIVONE ITS DIRECTORS, EMPLOYERS, STAFF NOR THE TITLE AND/OR INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHT HOLDERS MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE WARRANTIES OF USABILITY  FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR THAT THE CONTENT OR THE RESEARCH MATERIAL WILL NOT INFRINGE ANY THIRD PARTY PATENTS, COPYRIGHTS, TRADEMARKS OR ANY OTHER RIGHTS. THE READER ASSUMES ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR THE SELECTION OF THE CONTENT AND RESEARCH MATERIAL TO ACHIEVE READERS INTENDED RESULTS. IN THE EVENT THE WARRANTY EXCLUSION IS NOT VALID IN SOME JURISDICTION, THE READERS HEREBY ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT THE WARRANTY EXCLUSION SET FORTH IN THIS SECTION SHALL BE APPLIED TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY THE APPLICABLE LAW. Contacting Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd -  If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us by using the online Feedback Form, visiting the Contact Us page, or at the following address:# 5, 2nd floor, Crimson Court, Jeevan Bhima Nagar Main Road, HAL 3rd Stage, Bangalore - 560 075, India.Phone: +91 - 80 - 4153 7980 \ 81Last updated on 24-Feb-2012.Privacy Policy | Newsletter Opt-Out Policy | Disclaimer Newsletter Opt-Out PolicyTechTree.com offers a free electronic newsletter to users. Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove  themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database in order to stop receiving future communications:Using the online Feedback FormVisiting the Contact Us pageWriting to us at # 5, 2nd floor, Crimson Court, Jeevan Bhima Nagar Main Road, HAL 3rd Stage, Bangalore - 560 075, IndiaCalling us at +91 - 80 - 4153 7980 \ 81Privacy Policy | Newsletter Opt-Out Policy | DisclaimerDisclaimerThe contents of this website are based on information generally available to the public from sources believed to be reliable. No representation is made that it is timely, accurate or complete. Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd has taken due care and caution in compilation of data, as this has been obtained from various sources including which it considers reliable and first hand. However, Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd does not guarantee the accuracy, adequacy or completeness of any information and it is not responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of such information, and especially states that it has no financial liability whatsoever to the subscribers \ users of this website. The information herein, together with all estimates and forecasts, can change without notice.This website does not purport to be a solicitation of any advice pertaining to trade and business and readers are advised to consult experts or study \ evaluate individual business prospectus and other relevant legal documents before taking any decisions based on information provided in the site. Neither Trivone Digital Services Pvt Ltd nor its Directors or Analysts or Employees accept any liability whatsoever, nor do they accept responsibility for any financial consequences arising from the use of the research or information provided herein.Privacy Policy | Newsletter Opt-Out Policy | Disclaimer
News Corner Bobble AI bullish on growing business via regional content; announces dedicated keyboard in Malayalam Acer India launches business PC at Just Rs 9999 TCL 4K QLED with Hands Free AI TV Pre-booking Coming Soon at Reliance Digital Linksys India Launches VELOP MX5300 WIFI 6 Mesh System Acer introduces Nitro 5, its first 10th Gen Intel® Core™ Gaming Laptop Barco Introduces New Series of Advanced Video Processing and Presentation Control Systems NETGEAR Orbi RBK50 Mesh System to Augment Your Home Wi-Fi Network for Improved Work Efficiency Motorola announces its new flagship in India with the Fastest, Loudest, Boldest; motorola edge+ Surface Pro X, Surface Pro 7 and Surface Laptop 3 are now available in India Genelec Announces 1235A: Classic Heritage, Cutting Edge Performance
